kabn.network 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy

                                      Privacy Policy
1. Purpose
Our Privacy Policy explains how Crypto KABN Holdings Inc. and KABN (Gibraltar) Limited,
collectively (“KABN” or the “Company”) its subsidiaries, affiliate companies and the digital
on-boarding, Know-Your-Customer (KYC) and Anti-Money Laundering (AML) companies that
KABN works with collect, use, store and disclose your personal information. It also describes
the choices available to you concerning the use of, your access to, and how to update and
correct your personal information.
2. Scope
This Privacy Policy applies to personal information that KABN collects when you use or
access the Company’s web and mobile applications, kabn.network, and other Services
offered by KABN that mention this policy (collectively referred to as “Services”).
“Personal Information” is defined as any information about an identifiable individual.
Personal information will be handled by KABN in accordance with the Personal Information
Protection and Electronic Documents Act (“PIPEDA”) and this Privacy Policy.
3. Consent
When you sign up for a user account, KABN will ask for your express consent to the
collection, use, disclosure and retention of your personal information as outlined in this
Privacy Policy and for any other purposes identified to you at the time of collection. To
verify your identity, KABN will ask for your express consent to the collection, use, disclosure
and retention of specific personal information including ID documentation, and a “selfie”
picture of yourself. Additional documentation in the form of a utility bill or bank statement
may be required. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. However, if you
choose to withdraw your consent with respect to any information that KABN collects in
order to provide the Services to you, we will no longer be able to provide the Service to you.
You may always opt out of KABN’s collection, use and disclosure of your personal
information for any marketing purposes without affecting your use of the Services.
4. Security
KABN takes commercially reasonable measures to help safeguard your personal information
from loss, disclosure, alteration, misuse and unauthorized access, theft and destruction.
This includes, when required or appropriate and feasible, obtaining written assurances from
third parties that may access your data that they will protect the data with adequate
safeguards. As the internet is not 100% secure, KABN cannot guarantee the absolute
security of your information. We do not accept liability for unintentional disclosure. KABN is
        © 2019 Crypto KABN Holdings Inc. & KABN (Gibraltar) Limited. All rights reserved.

not responsible for the security of information that you transmit to us over networks that
the Company does not control, including the internet and wireless networks.
KABN retains information collected for no longer than is reasonably necessary to fulfill the
purposes for which the Company collects information and to comply with the Company’s
legal obligations.
If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, please contact us
at support@kabn.network.
5. Collection of Information
KABN collects the following types of information:
Information that you provide to KABN directly to deliver Services requested
     When you use the Services to register an account with KABN, the Company will collect
     your email address. When you use the Services to verify your identity through KABN, the
     Company will collect information such as ID Documents (passport, driver’s license, ID
     card, etc…), document type, scan of the document, country, “selfie” photo, account ID,
     legal name, national ID number, gender, date of birth, mailing address, IP address, user
     name, blockchain address, email, local storage, user display settings, Google
     authenticators, audit logs, and device camera. When you use the Services to verify your
     identity, KABN may collect information such as Social Insurance Number, credit records,
     telephone number, IP Address and utility bills.
Facial Biometric Identity Verification
     Facial biometric identity verification is accomplished by comparing two or more
     captured images of faces. The biometric identifiers used to complete this assessment
     are taken from the images that you submit.
Information we may collect from Third Parties
     KABN may collect information about you from other sources, including third parties that
     help the Company verify your eligibility for KABN Services. This information may be
     combined with personal information that has been collected about you under this
     Privacy Policy. Please note that the information KABN may receive from these third
     parties is governed by the privacy settings, policies, and/or procedures of the third
     parties.
6. Cookie Policy
     A cookie is a small text file that is placed and stored on your computer, mobile or other
     devices by webpages that you visit. The Cookies collect information in an anonymous
     form, including the number of visitors to the webpage, how the visitor found the
        © 2019 Crypto KABN Holdings Inc. & KABN (Gibraltar) Limited. All rights reserved.

   webpage and recent webpages visited. All cookies used by KABN are in accordance with
   current regulations.
   Before Cookies are placed on your device, you will be shown a pop-up requesting your
   consent to KABN’s use of Cookies. Your consent enables KABN to provide the best
   possible service to you.
   If you do not consent to the use of Cookies certain features of the KABN Service may not
   function as intended. You are also able to delete Cookies from your device at any time.
   KABN uses cookies for language selection and other semi persistent settings for visitors
   who are not signed in. KABN uses an encrypted session cookie for signed in users to
   identify who is signed in. Any other information in the encrypted session cookie is only
   available to read by our servers and should be treated as server data. It could include
   temporary messages or errors while using the app.
   KABN may also use any of the following categories of Cookies.
           1. Essential Cookies
               The Cookies are strictly necessary for the KABN website to function. They are
               usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a
               request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or
               filling in forms. These Cookies do not store any personally identifiable
               information.
           2. Analytics Cookies
               These Cookies track information about visits to the website so that we can
               make improvements and report performance. They help us to know which
               pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the
               site. All information these Cookies collect is aggregated and anonymous.
           3. Functional or Preference Cookies
               These Cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and
               personalisation. They are used to remember information you have entered
               or choices you make (i.e. username or language) on the KABN website. They
               may be set by KABN or by third party providers whose services we have
               added to our pages.
7. Use of Information
KABN may use the information collected from you for the following purposes:
       © 2019 Crypto KABN Holdings Inc. & KABN (Gibraltar) Limited. All rights reserved.

KABN may use personal information to provide products, Services or information requested
by you. Examples include to manage your individual information and account, help you
efficiently access your information after you sign in, allow access to certain functionalities
and features of the Company’s Services, and respond to your inquiries.
KABN may use personal information for the following administrative purposes:
    • Verify your identity
    • Process applications and transactions
    • Validate your identity with third parties of your choosing and upon your direction
    • Transfer your information that you choose to share with third parties upon your
        direction
    • Measure interest in KABN’s Services
    • Develop new products and Services or improve existing products and Services
    • Monitor metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns
        applicable to the Services
    • Send you Service-related emails (i.e., account verification, changes or updates to
        features of the Service, technical and security notice)
    • Compliance with legal obligations and regulatory requirements (i.e., respond to legal
        process or request for information issued by government authorities)
    • Prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities
    • Enforce KABN Terms and Conditions
8. Sharing of Information
KABN will not rent, share, transfer or sell your information to third parties without your
consent, except as noted in this Privacy Policy.
KABN may disclose information the Company collects in the following circumstances or as
otherwise described in this Privacy Policy:
With Vendors and Service Providers
    KABN may disclose your information to third party service providers that perform
    services on the Company’s behalf, such as web-hosting companies, analytics providers
    and information technology providers. KABN entrusts personal information to the
    following types of service providers:
                • Providers of IT and related services
                • Customer service activities
                • Fraud prevention
                • Providers of services you have requested
        © 2019 Crypto KABN Holdings Inc. & KABN (Gibraltar) Limited. All rights reserved.

   KABN has contracts with service providers that forbid them from using or disclosing
   personal information except as necessary to execute the contracted services on the
   Company’s behalf or to fulfil legal obligations.
With Law Enforcement or Government Authorities
   KABN may disclose information as may be permitted or required by laws of any
   jurisdiction that may apply to the Company, as provided for under contract, or as KABN
   deems reasonably necessary to provide legal services. In these circumstances, the
   Company takes reasonable efforts to notify you prior to disclosing information that may
   reasonably identify you, unless prior notice is prohibited by applicable law or is not
   possible or reasonable in the circumstances.
Change of Control
   If KABN sells or otherwise transfers part or the whole of KABN or the Company’s assets
   to another organization (i.e., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition,
   bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation), then your information may be sold or transferred
   as part of such a transaction as permitted by law and/or contract. The buyer or
   transferee will have to honour the commitments KABN has made in this Privacy Policy.
9. Individual’s Data Rights
   This section addresses how KABN handles requests pertaining to an individual’s rights as
   set out in the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
   You may contact us at support@kabn.network to inquire about your right to view all of
   the personal data that KABN has collected about you. Requests to access personal data
   will be answered within one month of receipt. A representative of KABN will provide
   more details during correspondence.
   You may contact us at support@kabn.network to request that KABN update or fix your
   personal data. Requests to rectify personal information will be answered within one
   month of receipt. A representative of KABN will provide more details during
   correspondence.
   You may contact us at support@kabn.network to request that KABN erase all of your
   personal data on file. KABN is only able to provide the Services through collection, use,
   storage, and sharing of your personal data. Without your personal data, KABN is unable
   to provide the Services requested. A request for the erasure of personal data equates to
   a request to be deleted from all KABN systems. Requests to erase personal data will be
   answered within one month of receipt. A representative of KABN will provide more
   details during correspondence.
       © 2019 Crypto KABN Holdings Inc. & KABN (Gibraltar) Limited. All rights reserved.

    You may contact us at support@kabn.network to request that KABN restrict the
    processing of your personal data. Requests to restrict processing will be answered
    within one month. A representative of KABN will provide more details during
    correspondence.
    You may contact us at support@kabn.network to request that KABN export all of your
    personal data on file. Personal data will be exported in a commonly used format.
    Requests to export data will be answered within one month. A representative of KABN
    will provide more details during correspondence.
10. Third Party Services and Content
The third party vendors with which KABN shares your personal information are
contractually required by the Company to keep this information confidential and may
generally not use such information for any purpose other than to help the Company provide
solutions to KABN customers.
KABN’s Services may include integrated content or links to content provided by third
parties. This Privacy Policy does not address the privacy, security, or other practice of the
third parties that provide such content.
KABN may use third party service providers to collect personal information on its behalf.
These third party service providers may be located in countries where the privacy laws
provide different levels of protection for personal information. If you would like more
information about KABN’s use of these service providers, please contact us at
support@kabn.network.
11. Retention
The Company retains personal information no longer than is necessary to fulfill the
purpose(s) for which it was collected, except where you have given permission for a longer
retention period or a longer period is permitted under applicable laws.
12. Updates or Changes to KABN Policies
KABN may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it
periodically. If the Company makes any material changes in the way it collects, uses, and/or
shares the personal information that you have provided, the Company will notify you by
posting notice of the changes in a clear manner. Your continued use of KABN’s Services
after any modification to this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such
modification.
13. Your Choices and Rights
       © 2019 Crypto KABN Holdings Inc. & KABN (Gibraltar) Limited. All rights reserved.

Subject to local law, you may have certain rights regarding information that KABN has
collected and that is related to you. Please contact KABN to update or correct your
information if it changes or if you believe that any information that we have collected about
you is inaccurate or out of date. You can also ask to see what personal information KABN
retains about you, and to erase your personal information. If you would like to exercise the
rights you may have, please contact us at support@kabn.network.
Although KABN strives to provide individuals with access to their personal information,
there may be instances where KABN may not provide access, including but not limited to:
where the information would put another individual’s privacy at risk, where the access
would reveal confidential commercial information, or the requested information contains
legal privilege. If KABN determines that access should be limited in any specific instance, the
Company will provide an explanation of why that assessment has been made and a contact
point for any further concerns.
If you no longer wish to receive marketing communications, please contact us.
14. Children’s Privacy
KABN does not knowingly collect or solicit any information from anyone under the age of 18
or knowingly allow such persons to register for the Service. The Service and its content are
not directed at children under the age of 18. In the event that KABN learns that the
Company has collected personal information from a child under the age of 18 without
parental consent, KABN will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe
that KABN might have any information from or about a child under 18, please contact the
Company.
15. Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at
support@kabn.network.
        © 2019 Crypto KABN Holdings Inc. & KABN (Gibraltar) Limited. All rights reserved.
